大家好，欢迎收听今日科技播客。今天是2025-06-12，我为大家带来536条最新科技资讯。
首先，让我们来看看今天的重点新闻。
第1条新闻：Build an LLM Web App in Python from Scratch: Part 4 (FastAPI, Background
Tasks SSE)。
据Dev。
to报道，Ever asked an AI to write a whole blog post, only to stare at a loading
spinner for five minutes, wondering if your browser crashed。
We've all been th.
第2条新闻：Stop Wasting Time Debugging Markdown Previews  Meet SubhDev。com.据Dev。
to报道，As developers, bloggers, or tech writers, we all know the struggle: You
write Markdown。
You want to see how it actually looks.You open up clunky desk.
第3条新闻：Gmsh FEA  CFD mesh generation with MATLAB。据Dev。
to报道，Gmsh Mesh Generator Gmsh is a very capable and cross platform stand-alone
open source mesh generator for FEA and CFD applications。
In addition to many.
第4条新闻：Hexagonal Rails: Escape the Framework Trap。据Dev。
to报道，Your Rails app is not your business。
Lets face it: most Rails codebases look like this: class OrdersController
ApplicationController def create order.
第5条新闻：Why do we still fall back to email for messages outside our usual tools。
据Dev。
to报道，In my intro post, I gave a quick overview of RelayBeam: a platform I built
to handle both internal and external communication in one place。
In this po.
接下来是今日科技快讯。
快讯1：C vs C  Still Relevant or Dead Languages?。
快讯2：Stop Wasting Time on Bad Email Data: A Developer's Guide to Email
Verification。
快讯3：大三自学笔记探索Hyperlane框架的心路历程。
以上就是今天的科技资讯播报。感谢大家的收听，我们明天同一时间再见。