大家好，欢迎收听今日科技播客。今天是2025-05-30，我为大家带来511条最新科技资讯。
首先，让我们来看看今天的重点新闻。
第1条新闻：How to Speed Up Frontend Development Without Sacrificing Flexibility。据Dev。
to报道，Lets be realfrontend dev has always been a balancing act between moving
fast and staying in control。
You can use page builders and get something up qu.
第2条新闻：Building a Bet Code Converter App: A Complete Guide。据Dev。
to报道，The online sports betting industry is growing rapidly across Africa,
Europe, and beyond。
With bettors using multiple platforms like SportyBet, 1xBet,.
第3条新闻：Harmonyos Cangjie Language Development Tutorial: Network Requests and Data
Parsing。
据Dev。
to报道，现在我能理解华为方面不断的鼓励大家在网络上贡献自己的教程没有教程没有参考文献仓颉购物应用的开发过程真是举步维艰每一步都是摸着石头过河不过希望通过幽蓝君的文章能让大家少走一些弯路
今天就以购物应用的分类列表为例分享在仓颉开发语言中如何进行网络请求以及怎么把请求到的数据展示到应用上 网络权限 网络权限在。
第4条新闻：I just started The Odin Project。
Curious to hear from anyone whos gone through it  how was your experience.
第5条新闻：Debugging EPUB Language Tags: How User Feedback Led to a Deep Dive into
Kindle's Font Selection Logic。
据Dev。to报道，TL;DR: Red Note users couldn't access Chinese fonts on Kindle。
Turns out, incorrect EPUB language metadata was the culprit.
Here's how we fixed it and.
接下来是今日科技快讯。
快讯1：HyperlaneRust 开发者的终极 Web 框架轻量又高性能。
快讯2：Rust Web 开发必备Hyperlane让 API 服务飞起来。
快讯3：The best navigation apps that work when you're completely disconnected。
以上就是今天的科技资讯播报。感谢大家的收听，我们明天同一时间再见。